kompakt.fm 2019-06-26

# Privacy @ Kompakt

## Supplier and responsible authority according to the Data Protection Act

Kompakt  
Mayer Paape Voigt GbR  
Werderstrasse 15-19  
DE-50672 Köln

##  Scope of application

In accordance with the Data Protection Act and the Telemedia Act, the following Privacy Statement has to inform the users of this website about the ways, the extent and the purpose personal data is collected and used by the website owner Mayer Paape Voigt GbR.

The website owner takes your privacy highly serious and treats your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the legal regulations. Please keep in mind that data transmission via the internet may involve gaps in security and cannot be completely protected from access by third parties.

## SSL-Encyption 

In order to protect your data in the best possible way, we're using SSL encryption for all requests. You recognize encrypted connections by reviewing the "https://" prefix of the current url in the browser location bar. Unprotected pages are prefixed with "http://". Thanks to SSL-encryption, all data you send to our website can not be read by third parties.

## Access data

The website owner or the provider of the website collects data about accesses to the page and stores the data as “Server-Logfiles“. The following data is taken down as follows:

  * Website visited
  * Current time as the time for access
  * Amount in byte of data sent
  * Source/Reference, from which you accessed the website
  * Browser used
  * Operating system used
  * IP-address used

The collected data only serve statistical evaluations and help to improve the website. The website owner, however, reserves the right to subsequently check the “Server-Logfiles“, if concrete indications suggest an unlawful use.

##  Handling of personal data

The website owner collects, uses and transfers your personal data only, if such actions are within the scope of the statutory framework or if you have agreed to data collection.

Personal data are defined as any information that serve to determine your person and can be traced back to your person like your name, your e-mail address and your phone number.

## Handling of contact data

As soon as you contact the website owner by using one of the provided contact possibilities, your contact details will be stored in order to be able to process and to reply to your request. Those data will not be passed on to third parties without your approval.

## Placing Orders

All data entered by a customer during the order process will be saved. This includes:

  * First name, last name
  * Address
  * Payment information
  * E-mail address

Those data, which are absolutely necessary for the delivery or order processing, are passed on to third service providers. As the storage of your data is no longer required or required by law, it will be deleted.

## Subscription to a newsletter

When you sign up to receive our newsletter, the data you provide will be used exclusively for this purpose. Subscribers may also be notified by email about circumstances relevant to the service or registration (such as changes to the newsletter offer or technical conditions).

For an effective registration we need a valid e-mail address. In order to verify that an application is actually made by the owner of an e-mail address, we use the "Double-opt-in" procedure. For this purpose we record the order of the newsletter and the receipt of the requested answer. The data will be used exclusively for newsletter distribution and will not be passed on to third parties.

The consent to the storage of your personal data and their use for the newsletter can be revoked at any time. Each newsletter has a link to it. You may also provide us with your request via the contact details provided at the end of this document.

The newsletter is sent via MailChimp which also stores the e-mail addresses and further information on the sending and analysis of the newsletter.

## Cookies

This website uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that will be stored on your device. Your browser accesses those files. By using cookies, the usability and security of your websites are of a higher quality.

Standard browsers allow to deactivate the use of cookies. Please note: It is not guaranteed that you can make use of all functions of this website without any limitations, if you make the appropriate settings.

## Google Analytics

This website uses “Google Analytics“, a service that is offered by Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA), in order to analyse the website usage by its users. The service uses cookies – text files, that are stored on your device. The collected information by using cookies will be transferred to and stored on a Google server based in the USA.

This website realises IP-anonymisation. The users‘ IP address will be shortened in all EU member states and within the European Economic Area. Thanks to the shortage, there is no personal connection to your IP address. The agreement on contracted data processing between the website owners and Google Inc. creates an evaluation of both the website usage and website activity by taking into account the collected data and provides services connected to internet usage.

You can avoid the storage of cookies on your device by making the appropriate settings in your browser. It is not guaranteed that you can make use of all functions of this website without any limitations, if your browser does not allow the use of cookies. Further, by using a browser plug-in you can prevent information, that has been collected using cookies, from being sent to and used by Google Inc. The following link provides you with the required plugin: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

For more information about the use of data by Google Inc. please click the following link: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>

## Registration on our website

If you register on our website to receive personalized services, personal data will be collected. These include the name, address, telephone number and e-mail address as contact and communication data.

The registration allows access to services and content that are only available to registered users. If required, registered users have the possibility to change or delete the data mentioned during the registration at any time. Of course, we will inform you on request which personal data has been collected and stored. In addition, we correct or delete the data on request, provided that the matter is not contrary to statutory retention requirements. For further questions as well as your request for correction or deletion of the data, please use the contact details stated in this privacy policy.

## Provision of paid services 

In order for us to provide paid services, we ask additional data. This applies, for example, to the details of payment. To ensure the security of your data during transmission, we use encryption techniques (such as SSL) over HTTPS that reflect the state of the art.

## Integration of services and contents of third parties 

Due to the complexity of today's data processing, we also depend on the support of external service providers. We use external agencies in connection with the collection and analysis of your usage data and we also depend on classic IT service providers.

So we are currently supported by Onlime Webhosting, Glaubtenstrasse 89, CH-8046 Zurich, which store your data and voluntary information for us and keep ready for use by us.

To detect and prevent a wide variety of attacks on our site, we use the services of Imperva Inc, 3400 Bridge Parkway, Suite 200, Redwood Shores, CA 94065, USA. All requests are routed in real-time through the Imperva network before passing the requests on to our servers, following an exclusively successful check.

As before, we are responsible for the security of your data. At the same time, these companies have pledged to us to take security precautions at a high level. Please note that a change of these service providers is possible at any time.

As far as we rely on the support of other or external service providers who store and process data for us in the context of data processing, these will also be bindingly incorporated into our data protection concept.

Our offer sometimes includes content, services and services of other providers. These are, for example, maps provided by Google Maps, videos from YouTube and Vimeo, audio from Soundcloud and Mixcloud as well as graphics and images from other websites. In order for these data to be accessed and displayed in the user's browser, the transmission of the IP address is absolutely necessary. The providers (hereinafter referred to as "third-party provider") thus perceive the IP address of the respective user. Although we endeavor to use only third-party providers who only need the IP address to deliver content, we have no control over whether the IP address may be stored. This process is used in the case, inter alia, statistical purposes. If we are aware that the IP address is being stored, we will inform our users.

## Social media profiles

We maintain online presences within social networks and platforms in order to communicate with customers, prospects and users to inform them about our services.

We point out that data of the users outside the area of ​​the European Union can be processed. This may result in risks for the users because e.g. enforcement of user rights could be made more difficult. With respect to US providers certified under the Privacy Shield, we point out that they are committed to respecting EU privacy standards.

Furthermore, the data of the users are usually processed for market research and advertising purposes. Thus, e.g. user profiles are created from the user behavior and the resulting interests of the users. The usage profiles can in turn be used to e.g. Place advertisements inside and outside the platforms that are allegedly in line with users' interests. For these purposes, cookies are usually stored on the computers of the users, in which the user behavior and the interests of the users are stored. Furthermore, in the usage profiles, data can also be stored independently of the devices used by the users (in particular if the users are members of the respective platforms and logged in to them).

The processing of the personal data of users is based on our legitimate interests in an effective information of users and communication with users in accordance with. Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f. DSGVO. If the users are asked by the respective providers for a consent to the data processing (that is, they declare their agreement, for example, by ticking a check box or confirming a button), the legal basis of the processing is Art. 6 para. a., Art. 7 GDPR.

For a detailed description of the respective processing and the possibilities of contradiction (opt-out), we refer to the following linked information of the provider.

Also in the case of requests for information and the assertion of user rights, we point out that these can be claimed most effectively from the providers. Only the providers have access to the data of the users and can directly take appropriate measures and provide information. If you still need help, then you can contact us.

**Facebook** (Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Irland) - Privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>, Opt-Out: <https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads> und [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/), Privacy Shield: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active).

**Google / YouTube** (Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA) – Privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>, Opt-Out: <https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated>, Privacy Shield: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active).

**Instagram** (Instagram Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA, 94025, USA) – Privacy policy/Opt-Out: <http://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/>.

**Twitter** (Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA) - Privacy policy: <https://twitter.com/de/privacy>, Opt-Out: <https://twitter.com/personalization>, Privacy Shield: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TORzAAO&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TORzAAO&status=Active).

**Pinterest** (Pinterest Inc., 635 High Street, Palo Alto, CA, 94301, USA) – Privacy policy/Opt-Out: <https://about.pinterest.com/de/privacy-policy>.

**Soundcloud** (SoundCloud Limited, Rheinsberger Str. 76/77, 10115 Berlin) - Privacy policy: <https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy>

**Mixcloud** (Mixcloud Limited, 96 Leonard Street, London, EC2A 4RH, United Kingdom) - Privacy policy: <https://www.mixcloud.com/privacy/>

**Bandcamp** (Bandcamp, 178 Castro St., San Francisco, CA 94114, USA) - Privacy policy: <https://bandcamp.com/privacy>

**Linkfire** (Linkfire ApS, Artillerivej 86, 3rd Floor, 2300, Copenhagen, Denmark) - Privacy policy: <https://linkfire.com/privacy>

## Data minimisation

Personal data is stored according to the principles of data avoidance and data minimisation only as long as required or prescribed by law (legal storage period). If the purpose of the information collected is omitted or the storage period ends, we block or delete the data.

## Rights of the user: information, correction and deletion

As a user, you will receive, at your request, free information about which personal data has been stored about you. If your request does not conflict with a legal obligation to retain data (eg data retention), you are entitled to correct incorrect data and to block or delete your personal data.

## Contact for privacy protection

If you have any questions about the collection, processing or use of your personal data, information, rectification, blocking or deletion of data and revocation of your consent, please contact our internal Privacy Coordinator: privacy@kompakt.fm

## Data Protection Officer

Dr.-Ing. Volker Till holds the position of Data Protection Officer and is available to you for concerns regarding data protection: privacy@kompakt.fm

Kompakt, Mai 2018
